# Katri Morrison-Goulias

katrialexandra@gmail.com | 805-403-6119 | Phoenix, Arizona

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/katri-morrison-goulias/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/katri-morrison-goulias/</a> | Github: <a href="https://github.com/katrimg">https://github.com/katrimg</a> | Portfolio: <a href="https://katrimg.github.io/basic-portfolio/">https://katrimg.github.io/basic-portfolio/</a>

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Passionate UX/UI Web Designer. Graduated with a BS from Arizona State University in Graphic Information Technology, and certificate in Web Development through the University of Arizona. Experienced in marketing and sales, and thrives in a team environment. Great problem solver, and enjoys creating user friendly designs.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Node.Js, JavaScript, jQuery, GIT, Github, Firebase, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, AJAX, React.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express & Handlebars JS, Illustrator, InDesign

#### **PROJECTS**

**Looking for Group** | React.js, MongoDB, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Media Queries | **Front-end Development & UX/UI Design** 

Web application for users looking to form groups with other Overwatch players. The app allows users to create an account, create groups, search and join other user's groups, and message within groups.

- Uses MongoDB to store data
- Utilizes React, Bootstrap, CSS, and Media Queries

#### Contributions:

- Created wireframes for the site's design
- Set up React Components
- Create Modals
- Completed UI Design of site using CSS & Bootstrap
- Utilized Mobile-first styling using Media Queries

Github: https://github.com/maxyeamans/lfg

Deployed: https://lit-oasis-62627.herokuapp.com/

## Concert Search | Javascript, API's, AJAX |

#### **Front-end Development**

Web application returning ticket information from Ticket Master, as well as top songs on spotify from searched artists.

- Uses Firebase to store user data
- Utilizes Bootstrap, CSS, and Materialize
- Integrates Ticket Master API and Spotify API

#### Contributions:

- Created mockups for site design using Illustrator
- Created main page background image using Illustrator
- Completed UI design using Bootstrap, CSS, and Materialize

Github: https://github.com/nikolaizemlin/Project 1

Deployed: https://nikolaizemlin.github.io/Project 1/main.html#

# WORK EXPERIENCE Grand Central Clothing

02/2018-Present

Key Holder

- Assists customers with their shopping needs
- Works in a team setting daily to complete tasks, and meet sales goals

#### **American Income Life**

04/2017-07/2017

Hiring Manager

- Conducted 5+ in-person interviews daily with potential employees
- Conducted 50+ phone-interviews daily
- Created promotional materials for management that improved recruitment

### **Bridal by Blake Patricia**

08/2016-01/2016

Graphic Design Intern

- Managed social media pages for 5 clients
- Planned and marketed events
- Created 100+ graphics for Bridal by Blake and client's

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Arizona**

Gilbert, AZ

04/2018-10/2018

Boot Camp - Web Development Certificate

An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications. Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars JS, & React Js.

#### **Arizona State University**

Tempe, AZ

08/2014-05/2018

B.S. Graphic Information Technology

Primary focus in Web Development with a Secondary focus in Business